# MOHAMED DIOP

#### SUMMARY

Hello there. My name is Mohamed and I consider myself a life long learner. I've started programming 8 years ago. I love technology and have a background in business that's why I never hesitate to get my feet wet with the latest stuff. This makes me polyvalent and adaptable. I highly enjoy work that goes beyond the common and pride my self with courtesy and intellectual curiosity above all.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **Software Engineer**

American Marketing Association, Southern California Chapter | Los Angeles, CA | March 2022 - Current

 Planning and creating a virtual art gallery to educate artists in underserved communities about the possibilities brought about by blockchain technology.
Specifically NFTs.

## Full Stack Software Engineer Immersive

General Assembly | Los Angeles, California | September 2021 - December 2021

• Re-studied Computer Science, Node.js, Django and much more.

# **ERP Implementation Consultant**

One Age Group | Dakar, Senegal | March 2020 - August 2021

 Led stakeholder presentations, building case for product implementation and showcasing solutions in real-world scenarios.

# Full Stack Mobile App Developer

Planet Kebab Dakar | Senegal | January 2020 - March 2020

- · Led design, research and development
- Technologies used were Docker, Node.js, MongoDB and React Native.

#### **Full Stack Software Engineer**

Internway Dakar | Senegal | January 2019 - December 2019

 Worked extensively with marketing and administrative teams to better understand market data in order to launch an intuitive solution for Internship seekers.

# **Data Analyst**

Wild Code School | Paris, France | September 2018 - December 2018

- Completed real world descriptive and inferential analysis using Python
- Used multiple data manipulation and artificial intelligence libraries such as Pandas, NumPy, SciPy, Scikit-learn, Tensorflow etc.

### Full Stack Software Engineer

Le Wagon | Lyon, France | January 2018 - March 2018

- Practiced the agile framework, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Ruby on rails, Git, test driven development, software architecture, data structures and algorithms, Big O notation, continuous integration, continuous delivery, SQL, fundamentals of cloud computing and much more.
- · Pitched a variety of real world projects.

## CONTACT

**3** 310-890-7695

• Los Angeles, CA 90005

## **PORTFOLIO**

• mohameddiopcodes.com

#### SKILLS

- · Software Development Lifecycle
- API design
- Data analytics
- SEO/Web Vitals
- Javascript
- Python
- Ruby
- JavaC/C#
- C/CII
- Solidity
- WebGL
- SQL/NoSQL
- Git
- · CI/CD
- Docker
- Cloud integration
- Full-stack Development

#### EDUCATION

# **Master of Science**

Computer Science Sup'Info Dakar

January 2021

### **Bachelor of Science**

Applied Mathematics And Computer Science

US3T

January 2019

#### DD A

Business Administration BEM/Kedge Business School, Dakar, Bordeaux September 2015

# LANGUAGES

English:

Full Professional

French:

Native/Bilingual